Wow!
So many people and carriages!
Let's see... The Royal Academy is...
Excuse me. Are you all right?
I suddenly started feeling ill...
Huh?!
Thank you. I feel better now.
I'm glad. You'll be all right now.
Thank you so much. How can I ever repay you?
You don't need to thank me.
It took a long time since I'm only level 1.
Oh, no. Who knows what would have
happened to my mother if not for you?
Wait, by any chance...
Were you on your way to the Royal Academy?
Yes, I'm moving into the dorm today.
Oh, then you'd better hurry!
Huh?
I believe the academy's
gates close at 6 o'clock.
What?!
Wait! Wait!
You're kidding...
It's time to lock the gate.
It's the rule that the Royal
Academy's main gate closes at 6 o'clock.
But the bell hasn't even finished ringing...
And now it has.
Your name and grade?
Alicia Ehnleit. I'm a new first-year.
Wait, the color of your necktie...
Aren't you a first-year, too?
Yes. I've been helping with the weekly duties
to get myself accustomed to the school.
In any case, the rules are absolute.
You'll have to find lodging
in town for tonight.
But the entrance ceremony is tomorrow.
I need to get into the dorm today.
Besides, um... I don't have that much money.
Oh, so you're the one commoner
who was admitted here this year.
Not that I don't sympathize...
But rules are rules. Just give up.
What?! But you're a first-year, too!
Meanie!
Now, what I'm about to say
is just me talking to myself.
Huh?
There's a part of the wall on the
eastern side that's crumbling.
Students who break curfew often
enter and leave through there.
You're unlikely to be seen at this hour.
What's your name?
Oh, I hadn't introduced
myself yet. How rude of me.
I'm Oswald Grimsarde.
Grimsarde? I've heard that
name somewhere before...
Probably my father. He's a
cabinet minister, after all.
You're the son of a minister?!
My father is my father, and I am
me. Please call me by my name.
Sure. I'll call you Oz, then.
O-Oz?
Thanks, Oz! You're a nice guy!
I hope we'll be friends!
Hand.
Huh?
You broke curfew too, right?
I'll help you in. Give me your hand.
C'mon.
Thanks.
Here we go. Ready, and... up!
You're really strong!
Just follow me.
I'm William Ares. You?
Alicia Ehnleit. Are you
a new first-year, too?
Yeah. The older guys in the dorm
sent me to buy drinks for a party.
See?
Oh...
It's sort of a ritual for
new kids entering the dorm.
Whoops...
Watch your step there.
Thanks. You really are strong, huh?
My dad's a general.
He's been training me since I was a kid.
A minister and a general...
All the people here are from
such impressive families.
Don't space out. If you're
not paying attention—
I-I... I can't!
What the?!
They just fell through the roof!
You okay?!
That... didn't hurt? What?
I'm the one who's hurting.
Would you mind getting off of me?
I'm so sorry! Are you all right?
Who are you?
My name is Alicia.
Hey, Ed. That had to hurt.
Ed? Are you two friends?
Yeah. I've known Will since we were kids.
I'm Edwin Valschein,
the second prince of the
Kingdom of Valschein.
A prince?!
Light Magic and the Hero
The only commoner
at the academy
Alicia
CV: Azumi Waki
Second prince of the
Kingdom of Valschein
Edwin
CV: Taku Yashiro
A swordsman with a
strong sense of justice
William
CV: Haruki Ishiya
An elite magic user
of high-ranking nobility
Oswald
CV: Kohei Amasaki
The strongest, most
passionate knight captain in the kingdom
Adolf
CV: Shinji Kawada
The apex of female
students and a tyrant
Eleonora
CV: Rina Hidaka
A girl attending the academy
Jessica
CV: Konomi Inagaki
A boy attending the academy
Patrick
CV: Yuma Uchida
The black-haired villainess
Yumiella
CV: Fairouz Ai
Light Magic and the Hero
We haven't even had the
entrance ceremony yet,
and you're already causing a commotion.
You don't waste time, do you?
As the principal, I feel that
makes you worth teaching.
This is all your fault.
What? Why me?
I got distracted 'cause you talked to me.
Excuse me?!
Quiet.
William Ares...
I'll be confiscating this.
And Alicia Ehnleit...
Y-Yes?
You have a rare and precious
talent for light magic.
That is why you were the one and only
commoner admitted here on a scholarship.
Always be aware of that, and mind
your behavior going forward.
I'm sorry.
You will both be given extra duties
for one week as punishment.
You are to work together, and no fighting.
You may go.
Pardon us.
I see. So that's Alicia Ehnleit.
She's our kingdom's last hope
of salvation from the Demon Lord...
I screwed up on my first day.
I showed up late, broke a window, and
even got punished with extra duties.
Intruder!
There's an intruder! Capture him!
Where'd he go?
He may have climbed the wall to get outside.
Go and look. I'll check the dorm.
Right!
There's been an intruder on school grounds!
All of you, stay inside!
Okay!
Got it!
Scary...
I guess bad guys target this
school since it's full of nobles?
But I'm safe on that front,
considering I'm a commoner.
Take that!
Someone—
Be quiet. I'm not a bad guy.
It's you!
Your name was... Alicia?
It's me. Remember, the
guy who broke your fall?
Edwin... Your Highness?!
Yeah, there's some stuff going on...
"Stuff"?
There's something I want to look into...
But when I tried to sneak into the
school building, they spotted me.
I can't tell you the details, but...
Find him?
I didn't see him anywhere.
I see. Stay on guard, though.
Got it.
I can't go out there yet.
Please, let me hide here for a while.
What?!
Sorry about this.
I know a gentleman shouldn't just
dive into a lady's room, but...
Oh, it's fine. This almost
feels like a dream.
I've never talked to a member
of the royal family before.
It's the same for me. I'm always
surrounded by royalty and nobles.
Are all commoner women as violent as you?
Don't be mean! I did that because
I thought you were a robber!
I'm just kidding. Please don't hit me again.
I suppose I owe you one now.
About what happened tonight...
Don't worry. I won't tell anyone.
I appreciate it.
I think the coast is clear now.
I don't want to trouble
you by staying too long.
See you at the entrance ceremony
tomorrow. Goodnight, Alicia.
Be careful, Prince Edwin.
The new students will now enter.
Oh, I'm sorry...
Is something the matter, Alicia Ehnleit?
H-How do you know my name?
I... just do.
More importantly, are you feeling ill?
I-I'm all right.
The Royal Academy Entrance
Ceremony will now commence.
Having the privilege to welcome you
first-years to our school today
gives all of us at the academy
the greatest pleasure.
As you are already aware...
That's enough, Yumiella!
That devil's luck of yours
is finally about to run out!
Now, Alicia!
Right!
Sacred light magic,
banish the darkness and grant me strength!
Alicia...
Edwin
Well done, Alicia.
Alicia
Thank you, Prince Edwin.
It's morning...
This game is called Light Magic and the Hero,
Light Magic and the Hero
or Light and Hero for short.
Light and Hero
It takes place in a world
of swords and magic.
Oswald
Not that I don't sympathize...
But rules are rules. Just give up.
The heroine enrolls in the Royal Academy,
where she deepens her relationships
with the conquerable characters
William
You broke curfew too, right?
I'll help you in. Give me your hand. C'mon.
as she levels up and, eventually,
defeats the Demon Lord.
Edwin
I suppose I owe you one now.
About what happened tonight...
It's a fairly cliché story.
But after the ending in which
the Demon Lord is defeated,
The Demon Lord is defeated, but...
A hidden boss has appeared.
the hidden boss, the game's
strongest foe, appears.
She is Yumiella Dolkness,
Yumiella...?!
the villainess who uses dark magic
Don't tell me you're...
and bullies the heroine,
Alicia, throughout the game.
I thought you seemed
suspicious...!
(We have to fight her?!)
And that's me.
At age fifteen,
I'm on my way to enter the
Royal Academy in the capital.
The Hidden Boss Enters the Academy
I was five years old when I regained
my memories from my previous life.
While I was attending college,
I got hit by a truck
and reincarnated in this world.
Some research confirmed
that this was, in fact,
the world of Light and
Hero, the game I played.
Pondering why it happened won't do any good.
All I know is that that's what happened.
This kingdom was founded by the hero
and saint who defeated the Demon Lord.
Because that Demon Lord was black-haired,
black hair is seen as unlucky,
and even as a symbol of evil.
That must be one of the things that
makes the villainess what she is.
Even my servants keep me at arm's length.
Also, I have no memory of ever meeting
my parents, who live in the capital.
The Demon Lord can be
defeated at level 70 or so,
but once Yumiella becomes the hidden boss,
one's level has to be
maxed out to defeat her.
She is truly the embodiment of unfairness.
But she still gets defeated in the end.
So does my existence really have any meaning?
Still, I thought...
I have the potential to
surpass even the final boss,
I'm stronger than anyone
in the heroine's party,
and I can use dark magic, which
only enemy characters can use.
Isn't that... actually awesome?!
Of course! There's no need to recreate the
story of Light and Hero to the letter!
William
Stop picking on Alicia. Don't make me angry.
Oswald
If that's how it must be, I have an idea.
I had no interest in the dating
sim aspect of the game.
Edwin
Stop messing with Alicia!
I had no emotional attachment to the
three conquerable characters, either.
So instead of living out the
story of Light and Hero,
I could just lay low and
enjoy a peaceful school life.
I'd have nothing to do with
Alicia or the male leads.
That way, I could avoid all risk
of becoming the hidden boss,
Edwin
Defeat the Demon Lord! Let's go, everyone!
and in the spring of our third year,
Alicia and the boys would defeat
the resurrected Demon Lord,
and we'd all live happily ever after.
But I should still raise
my level as much as I can.
I need to be strong enough to beat the
Demon Lord myself if it comes to that.
Yah.
It comes so naturally.
When you kill a monster,
you get a magic stone.
I should be able to sell these for money.
I think my movements are a little faster now.
Is this what leveling up feels like?
The gamer blood in me is boiling!
I was always the type to get
absorbed in what I was doing,
so I'd sneak out of the
mansion essentially every day
and get engrossed in leveling up.
On top of that, I made
money off of magic stones
and bought all kinds of items.
The first thing I bought
was the Amulet of Growth.
The Amulet of Protection would
be better for keeping me safe,
but wearing this would allow
me to level up much faster.
Then, I entered the dungeon.
I'll be fine by myself.
I can regenerate an arm
with my magic if I need to.
I conquered it.
I also acquired the Monster-Calling Flute.
And day...
after day...
Until today, at age fifteen,
I've focused only on leveling up efficiently.
I've been through the same dungeon
from start to end countless times.
I hope I'll be able to continue
leveling up after I start school.
Even the building looks just
like it did in the game.
I'm exhausted.
Attend the Royal Academy.
While there, befriend as many sons
of high-ranking noblemen as you can.
They don't need to be eldest sons, as I'll
have one marry you and become my heir.
And this is my first
interaction with my parents?
I should...
It's time to lock the gate.
It's the rule that the Royal
Academy's main gate closes at 6 o'clock.
But the bell hasn't even finished ringing...
It's really playing out just
like it did in Light and Hero.
Wait, the color of your necktie...
Aren't you a first-year, too?
Avoid getting involved with those four.
That's the key to having a peaceful life.
The new students will now enter.
The Royal Academy Entrance
Ceremony will now commence.
Having the privilege to welcome you
first-years to our school today
gives all of us at the academy
the greatest pleasure.
As you are already aware...
I feel eyes on me.
Oh, right. It must be my hair.
We will now assess your levels.
What? Assess our levels?
Alicia Ehnleit: level 1.
Work your hardest going forward.
I will.
What is my level, anyway?
Come to think of it, I've never checked...
William Ares: level 10.
Whoa!
Incredible!
Yeah, I guess!
They're that excited over level 10?
Then if I don't want to stand out,
I hope I'm... around level 5?
Level 5...
wouldn't be enough to beat a boss character.
Miss Yumiella Dolkness.
Yes, sir.
Are you nervous?
Don't worry. There's nothing embarrassing
about being level 1 when you start school.
No, that's not why I'm nervous.
Eldest daughter of Count
Dolkness, Yumiella Dolkness...
L-Level 99?!
What?!
For real?!
Level 99?!
Well... goodbye to my peaceful life...
Villainess Level 99
I May Be the Hidden Boss but I'm Not the Demon Lord